https://www.suretek.com.au/refund-policy/

BECOME A CUSTOMER
1300 65 44 33HomeAbout UsNewsPodcastsTrainingCareersMonitoringCAMSRemoteGUARD1300-1345Co-locationManaged NetworkAlarmLINKAlarm CommunicatorsM2MMulticomSurepollTechToolsSurveillanceAsustorAvigilonRaytecMySuretekContactHomeAbout UsNewsPodcastsTrainingCareersMonitoringCAMSRemoteGUARD1300-1345Co-locationManaged NetworkAlarmLINKAlarm CommunicatorsM2MMulticomSurepollTechToolsSurveillanceAsustorAvigilonRaytecMySuretekContactBecome a CustomerRefund PolicyWe are happy to provide an exchange/replacement product if the goods you have received are defective in some way subject to the terms of this Refund/Return Policy. Full refunds including shipping costs will be available in the instance of major faults/defects as per Australian Consumer Law. To process your return and possible exchange, we require a receipt or proof of purchase. Please do not send your purchase back to the manufacturer.If you have not received your goods within 30 days of the estimated delivery date you may be eligible for being sent replacement goods. Please contact us via the Contact Form on our web site if you have not received your goods within these time-frames.Please note that any item that is a) not defective in some way, and b) not in its original condition, is not returnable. Any item that is not returned within 30 days of receipt by you is not returnable.Shipping costs
You are responsible for the cost of returning any goods to us in accordance with this Refund/Return Policy. Shipping costs are non-refundable. We are responsible for costs of shipping any replacement goods to you where applicable.Sending your return
When returning goods in accordance with this Refund/Return Policy, please send to:Suretek
12 to 16 Bentley St
Wetherill Park, NSW 2164
AustraliaInsurance
Please consider using a trackable shipping service or purchasing shipping insurance when sending your return. We cannot be responsible for any loss of goods in transit.Processing of returns
Once your return is received and inspected by us we will send you an email to notify you that we have received your returned item. We will also notify you of the approval or rejection of your exchange/replacement request.Replacement timeframes
We process any exchange/replacement requests regularly. Please allow 14 days for us to process your exchange/replacement request, plus any applicable shipping time. Please contact us via the Contact Form on the web site to enquire as to the status of your exchange/replacement request.Collection of your Personal InformationSuretek collects personally identifiable information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address or telephone number. Suretek also collects anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your ZIP code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites.There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by Suretek. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring Web site addresses. This information is used by Suretek for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Suretek Web site.Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through Suretek public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others. Note: Suretek does not read any of your private online communications.Suretek encourages you to review the privacy statements of Web sites you choose to link to from Suretek so that you can understand how those Web sites collect, use and share your information. Suretek is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on Web sites outside of the Suretek and Suretek family of Web sites.Use of your Personal InformationSuretek collects and uses your personal information to operate the Suretek Web site and deliver the services you have requested. Suretek also uses your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Suretek and its affiliates. Suretek may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.Suretek does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. Suretek may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. In addition, Suretek may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Suretek, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.Suretek does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.Suretek keeps track of the Web sites and pages our customers visit within Suretek, in order to determine what Suretek services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within Suretek to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.Suretek Web sites will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Suretek or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Suretek; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Suretek, or the public.Use of CookiesThe Suretek Web site use "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize Suretek pages, or register with Suretek site or services, a cookie helps Suretek to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same Suretek Web site, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Suretek features that you customized.You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Suretek services or Web sites you visit.Security of your Personal InformationSuretek secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. Suretek secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other Web sites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.Changes to this StatementSuretek will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. Suretek encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Suretek is protecting your information.Contact InformationSuretek welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Suretek has not adhered to this Statement, please contact Suretek. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.×
We use cookies on our website. If you continue, we will assume that you are happy with it.AcceptPrivacy Policy
